The Princess Sapphire
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Princess Knight,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Second Episode
The Daughter of Mephisto
I feel it, this is the moment!
Finally I have found
that girl!
I soldiers have already
collected the taxes!
You won't steal any more money!
- Stop him!
- But who is that knight?
He broke all the sacks!
That damned bastard won't
stop us from collecting the taxes!
I told you that you have
to pay the new taxes.
I don't have a single penny left!
Pay what you have to pay
or you will pay with your life!
Please, have mercy!
So you didn't have any money, huh?
And what is this?
But that's the little bit
I need to live on!
Shut up! And now you want to live too?
Why don't you leave
this poor man alone?
But I have nothing to do with it! I was ordered
to collect the new taxes,
but this man doesn't want to pay!
So you are Duralumin's
men, right?
That's none of your business!
And who do you think you are?
Prince Sapphire!
Kid, are you trying to mock us?
this little fool says he is
Prince Sapphire!
- A Prince without an escort!
- He's just a brat!
- Let's get rid of him quickly.
- If you don't disappear, I'll skewer you!
Idiot! The brat is over there!
But it's not me you're supposed to skewer!
It's that guy over there, you idiot!
There is nothing to laugh about!
It's over for you, brat!
Then come on, bring it on!
I'm not afraid of you at all!
Your choice:
either the taxes or jail!
- Damn, I'm pinned down!
- Nice shot! Now let's finish him!
Good! Leave him to me!
Don't you get it that
the brat is over there?!
I'll tell my father everything!
Come down, Prince! It's time
for you to return to the palace!
But where has he gone?
Come here, Opal!
Hello, Prince! Forgive
the rudeness of my men!
So it really is the Prince!
Make them return the money
they took from the villagers!
Let's split it, Prince, so we can
both have fun with that money.
I don't want that money!
You must return it!
Very well, Prince, I will
do as you command.
Good!
That brat is insolent!
You, blockheads,
continue the tax collection!
Spread the word that the money
is needed by the Prince for a castle!
Hand over the money!
The Prince must
build himself a castle!
And what are you doing, slacker?
Go collect the taxes! Move it!
Hecate, I have finally found
the girl I was looking for!
A girl?! Do you
mean that Prince, dad?
Yes! She is a female,
but with a boy's heart!
It's a mistake that Heaven
makes every 2,000 years.
Oh, poor thing! How
sorry I feel for her!
I am convinced that you would
become an excellent witch...
..if you could exchange
your heart for hers.
Come, infernal winds! Honor
my daughter Hecate, lightning!
Thunder! Wind! Lightning bolts!
Stir, scourges of hell!
And you, hurricanes, celebrate
the beauty of my daughter!
Now, Hecate, you
too will try to...
Hecate, where did you
go? Hecate! Where are you?
My father would like me to be different
from how I am, you know, little bird?
Hecate! Aren't you ashamed
of keeping flowers in your hair?
...and little birds in your hand? Change
the flowers into something ugly!
Hail Mephisto!
Why did you transform it
on my head?!
- Try with a storm, come on!
- Come, lightning!
Blow, wind!
Fall, rain!
- Well?!
- I can't do it!
Don't cry, my little witch!
We'll find a remedy!
I will have you take
a course in witchcraft,
so you will become an excellent witch!
Hail Mephisto!
Who was it?
Who threw water on me?
Ah, it was you!
I wish I could fly too
in the sky, just like you do.
What do you say? Would you take me
for a little ride?
I'm ready! You can go!
Hey!
Hello, Sapphire!
- Tink! Where are you going?
- I'm having a little fun flying!
Wait, I'm coming too!
No! The strings can't take it!
We would be too heavy!
Magnificent!
Fly high!
Even higher! Even
further up, come on!
Higher and higher, friends!
Watch out, Sapphire!
You are too heavy!
I must try not to
touch the treetops!
The swans can't make it! Now
you are too close to the ground!
I apologize,
Mr. Bull! I apologize!
Help! I'm going to
crash into a house!
Forgive me, I really
wasn't able to avoid it.
We worked day and
night to build this house.
But I thought it was a pigsty!
- Boy, how dare you?!
- How dare you?!
It is not by our choice
that we live in this hut!
Our house was destroyed
by the Grand Duke's henchmen,
so we were forced
to live miserably!
- They did this to you?! - Yes! They
took everything we had!
They told us
that the usual taxes are not enough,
so we have to pay more,
because the Prince
must build himself a castle!
- Prince Sapphire is to blame!
- He is a stupid Prince!
They lied to you! I don't have to
build myself any castle!
- But then you are...!
- Our Prince Sapphire!
- is it really you?!
- I must speak to the Grand Duke!
Where did Sapphire go?
Well, I have the impression that Mephisto
is lurking right around here.
We must find him immediately, Opal!
Where are you, Sapphire?
Answer if you hear me! Sapphire!
Oh, what a magnificent castle!
It is truly huge! Make yourself more comfortable,
don't get too worked up.
I have an idea!
Now it all depends on you, Opal!
I'm counting on you!
Prince Sapphire is entering
the castle!
I want to see
Grand Duke Duralumin!
The Grand Duke has gone hunting!
- Then I will wait for him inside!
- You can't!
What did you say?! - I was joking!
Please, forgive me!
Let's go to the apartments
of the Grand Duke!
What a beautiful house!
Some have too much and some have nothing, eh!
Prince Sapphire is here, Grand Duke
He is bringing along
some strange people.
Isn't it a stroke of luck
that he came to you?
- I think I understand.
- You could kill him now,
without anyone knowing.
I will not allow
Sapphire to be killed!
That bust is speaking!
Sapphire is mine!
No one must touch him!
Show yourself! Who are you?
You don't scare us,
whoever you are!
I am Mephisto!
And you will do as I say.
Excuse me, Mephisto, why does Sapphire
interest you so much?
I must transplant the heart
of Sapphire into my daughter's chest,
that way I will succeed in
making her a great witch!
Doing something like
that is truly impossible!
I am Mephisto! For me,
everything is possible!
Look! Turn into flowers!
But this is a cheap trick!
Insolent! "Cheap", you said?
Then I'll show you!
- Do you like an electric cape?
- Ouch, that hurts!
And if you're not convinced...
Hail Mephisto!
Are you convinced,
now, of my power?
Yes, Mephisto! But what
will happen to Sapphire...
...when will you succeed in taking
his boy's heart?
She will only become
an ordinary girl
But that is what we want too!
Listen, Grand Duke,
Mephisto can be of use to you.
If he makes the Prince
a girl, the throne will be yours.
Lord of darkness, I pay
homage to you! I have decided to help you.
That's fine!
Then bring Sapphire here to me!
I'm running to call him!
Grand Duke, I know you are at the castle!
Show yourself! I must speak with you!
Prince, please come in! We have
prepared a worthy welcome for you!
I am only here to ask
the Grand Duke...
...why he had the house
of these men destroyed!
Don't worry, I just wanted
to compensate them for the damage suffered.
Here! These provisions are for you!
- And now scram!
- Thank you, sir! We are grateful to you!
This way, please.
The Grand Duke is waiting for you.
Where is the Grand Duke? I don't see him here.
- Sapphire! It's me: Tink!
- Stop!
You cannot enter the castle of
the Grand Duke without permission!
This will be the end of the Prince.
Come, Grand Duke, show
yourself! I would like to speak to you!
Damned monster!
I will annihilate you!
I understand: you are Mephisto!
Well, little Prince! I am
truly glad to meet you!
For a long time I have been
waiting for this day to arrive!
What do you want from me?
Your heart, so fearless that
it does not fear the devil!
If you really want it,
you'll have to conquer it!
- Just you and me, Mephisto!
- Go, Mephisto!
- Damnation!
- May he fall into my power!
- I feel paralyzed!
I can no longer feel my muscles!
Now you are in my hands and nothing
more will stop me from taking your heart!
Diabolical hands,
emanate your infernal fluid...
..that envelops every
mortal in a shroud of sleep!
We did well
to ally with the devil!
And who could that be? You
go and see who it is, Baron!
Sapphire!
Sapphire! Sapphire! Wake
up! Don't go near him!
How dare you?! I..
Ah, I'm paralyzed!
- Mephisto!
- Break the spell!
Now I recognize you: you are
an angel! I will have my revenge!
Wait! Fall down the stairs!
Wait! Wait!
Damn it,
we almost made it!
Mephisto, you have really
disappointed me! Really!
- You were saying?
- You let yourself be fooled like a novice!
I couldn't do anything!
That child is an angel!
An angel?!
An angel
is a difficult opponent.
- Nylon!
- Yes, Grand Duke?
- Get that nose out of my face!
- Is this okay, Grand Duke?
- We must kill that boy.
- Yes, sir!
Sapphire, wake up! He's still
unconscious! I must look for some water.
I'll splash it on his face, like this...
Ah, my nose! My nose!
- I captured him, Grand Duke!
- The boy has left you in quite a bad way.
Don't come near me!
Take him away! He'll disintegrate us!
- Yes! yes! yes!
- You can continue your work.
Hail Mephisto! Infernal forces!
Emanate from my hands
and envelop the Prince!
May he be lifted into the air!
May he be brought to my lair!
- Thank you for your help!
- You're welcome, Mephisto.
Hail Mephisto!
Now the throne will be mine!
You will stay up there until
the eagles devour you!
Long live the Baron!
I can't manage to free myself!
The knots are too tight!
I'm very worried about Sapphire!
I am not your breakfast! If you want
to scare me, you've succeeded!
Now go away, otherwise..
more will come!
Dark forces of evil,
of the underworld and of darkness,
rise from the eternal fire
and from the cold of the graves!
I, Mephisto, your master,
call you!
Hail Mephisto!
Enter! Come into the crucible
of my black magic alchemy!
Hecate! Lie down on the table!
You are about to become
a great witch!
I will give you the heart and the courage
of this girl, soon!
This magic potion
will release the energy of evil within you!
Rise, tree of wickedness!
Help me execute my work!
I command you!
The moment has come! My
masterpiece will be completed!
Help! Help! Will you stop it?
I won't make it! Go away!
Help!
Help! Help!
Look! There's a shoe
fallen from the sky!
What happened? Let's go see!
What do I see! Brothers, over
there is a child hanging from a tree!
- What do we do?
- We must help him!
- Before they devour him!
- Quick, brothers, let's run!
Don't start cutting from
where I'm cutting, eh!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Idiot! This is the tree!
They are helping me!
Let's get out from under the tree!
Yes, that's fine!
Look, a ravine!
We won't make it across!
If we cut down that tree,
it can serve us as a bridge!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Now you can cross
the ravine.
- And aren't you coming? - The ravine
marks the border of the land.
- We are forbidden to go beyond.
- Then goodbye, friends!
Goodbye!
Come,
infernal and occult forces!
Guide me, demon brothers!
Hold my hand tight!
Now I will take her heart!
Sapphire!
What?! Tree of evil, stop
that angel from approaching!
You won't make it through!
That's what you think!
You must suffocate him!
- Take this!
- What do you think you're doing?!
Damn it!
I'll get you, damned feather!
Help! My eye!
La formula, Hecate!
Hail Mephisto! Disappear, feather!
The tree of evil will die!
Don't dare to come near!
See what you've done,
Hecate? Stop that angel!
I'm taking the girl away!
Hail Mephisto!
Infernal frog!
Hey! What is that?
Infernal tarantula!
It wants to catch me with that thread!
It's useless for you to hide,
Mephisto! I know you're not far!
They are cannons!
I destroyed it!
Sapphire, wake up!
- Tink!
- Yes, Sapphire, it's me!
Tell me, Tink, where am I?
You're in Mephisto's lair! Look!
Hail Mephisto!
Mephisto! This time
you won't defeat me! Wait for me
Sapphire!
Here is another monster!
Rise, immense monster!
And devour Sapphire!
- Stop!
- It's terrifying!
It's getting closer!
Now it's moving the mountain!
Take this and drink it!
I hope you like it!
I order you to devour them!
Take this!
So you want a fight to the
death! Mountain, sink!
What's happening?
Help!
What's happening? It's all vanished!
- Sapphire!
- I don't understand.
I don't understand
what happened either!
Someone must have helped you!
Maybe it was Hecate!
Hecate, come here immediately!
Was it you who helped
the Princess?
Dad, I'm sorry to confess it,
but it was me.
But my daughter, it is for you
that I did all this!
I wanted it for your own good, to
make you become an excellent witch!
Instead, you helped Sapphire!
Why did you do it?
Because I don't want to become
a witch when I grow up.
Little degenerate, unnatural and
unworthy daughter of your father!
But I won't give up! One day, I
will succeed in taking your heart...
...to give it to my daughter
Hecate! Remember that!
That little girl will
never become a witch.
- She's too good!
- Yes, she really is good.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP